surveyspaid.com 2007-09-15

# SurveysPaid.com - Earn money by filling out online surveys!

SurveysPaid.com takes your privacy very seriously. We will not sell or share any of your information to any third party websites. Your credit card information is kept private and is maintained by a secure third party website. 

**What information does SurveysPaid.com collect from you?**

SurveysPaid.com may collect information such as the URL you came to SurveysPaid.com from, your IP address, your browser type, country of origin, length of time spent at our site and other usage statistics. This information is used by SurveysPaid.com exclusively. This information is used to analyze trends and get a better idea of how to serve our members. SurveysPaid.com also collects some personal information. This includes but is not limited to your email address and name. This is used to confirm your identity in case you lose your password. This information is not shared with anyone and is stored on third party secure server. SurveysPaid.com is not responsible if database information is hacked or stolen from the third party secure server, however, this is very unlikely to occur.

**With whom do we share your information?**

SurveysPaid.com will not release any personal information to third party other than as outlined in this privacy policy. Members grant SurveysPaid.com the right to use this information internally without restrictions for the purposes of, but not limited to, research, marketing, and content development. Please be advised that the content listed on SurveysPaid.com is not owned nor maintained by SurveysPaid.com. When signing up for surveys or other types of offers, we are not responsible for what they do with your information or for any damages that may occur. Please review their privacy policy before you sign up for anything.

**Email Communication**

We may from time to time send you e-mail or other communications regarding current promotions, specials and new additions to the SurveysPaid.com site, important changes in our program, Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy etc. With your registered membership, you may receive special surveys, newsletter, reward incentives and offers sent from SurveysPaid.com.

**Security Precautions**

In order to most efficiently serve you, established third party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions handle credit card transactions and order delivery. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order. All information pertaining to the member database is updated frequently and stored offline as well. SurveysPaid.com takes precautions to protect against fraud, hacking or the altering of databases.

**Children's Privacy**

You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site. Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are the parent or guardian of a minor under 18 years of age and believe that they have disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at privacy@SurveysPaid.com so that we may delete the minor's information.

**You should carefully review privacy policies of any third party sites accessible from SurveysPaid.com**

Other sites accessible through our web site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. SurveysPaid.com is not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Please be aware that this site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those web sites linked to SurveysPaid.com. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. On behalf of various sponsors, SurveysPaid.com provides sponsored links to third-party web sites. If you click on a sponsored link or banner ad, a "window" or "frame" containing a third-party's web site may appear in the foreground with the SurveysPaid.com web site in the background. Unless you are on SurveysPaid.com's web site, any time that you have moved to a window, you should assume that your personal information is being collected, used and disclosed in accordance with the windowed site's privacy policy (if any).

**Transfer Assignment**

SurveysPaid.com reserves the right to assign the ownership of the site, databases, intellectual property and all information contained within the Web site upon sale or acquisition to another entity. Members will be notified of such sale or acquisition by email and it will be posted on the site. We are not responsible for notifying you beyond the email address provied at the time you became a member. If you wish to update this information, please email webmaster@surveyspaid.com

**Contacting SurveysPaid.com about privacy questions or concerns**

You can contact SurveysPaid.com in a number of ways that can be found in our Contact Us section. If you choose to correspond via email, SurveysPaid.com uses email links located throughout the site to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. You may also contact us by e-mail at privacy@SurveysPaid.com

**Privacy Policy Disclaimer**

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.
